<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Infodump on WorkSpace</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/infodump/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Infodump on WorkSpace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 23:12:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/infodump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>97X-BAM!</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/08/20/charlie-babbitt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 23:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/08/20/charlie-babbitt/</guid>
      <description>WorkSpace has the best PR. This should be no surprise as they also have the best of everything else; cherry picking was second nature to the myriad minds that ran the corporation. PR had to be good, they had the unenviable task of shoehorning an essentially incompatible prickly cactus cock of corporate reality into a sheath of barrier protection – there was no way that the public would allow the stark reality of WorkSpace realities into their lives without the blinkering cosmesis of spin to lube the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mute</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/08/09/mute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 11:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/08/09/mute/</guid>
      <description>It lived in the sun. It thought with light. It was a tethered god. It is the largest living being on the planet.
From low earth orbit, perhaps 350 kilometres up, India is a stunning splinter of silver, a concentrated kernel of thermonuclear ur-light that whips around every ninety minutes, a man-made quasar in all but name. The National Solar Mission started in the 2010s was at the time the largest solar power initiative on the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Critical Depth</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/05/25/instruction-creep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 17:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/05/25/instruction-creep/</guid>
      <description>It turned out that saving the world was a bit of a let down, there was just so much crap to deal with. When he was at the Madhom yard (and when he had had the energy to think about it), it had seemed simple: Remove the bloatware management goons, up the base-level day rate by an order of magnitude and decree a 5-day working week. Not without a substantial amount of irritation he learned the same lesson that a thousand previous owner/managers had learned the hard way – the hundred and one ills and wrongs committed by the management are just the poorly articulated output of a deeply imperfect machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What it&#39;s like not to believe</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/10/21/what-its-like-not-to-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 21:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/10/21/what-its-like-not-to-believe/</guid>
      <description>Deep down in the WorkSpace corporate lexicon, somewhere between WashWord (ref: outbound content checks), and Weasel (mid management slang: derogatory) is: WASTE. Terminologies rated corporate pivotal (i.e.: relating to criteria rated indistinguishable from the basic genetics of the WorkSpace raison d’etre) are always fully textually capitalised, and are mandated to remain so always. WASTE (implying a keen imperative to avoid profligacy) is one of the big three, one third of the corporate triadic indivisible from the notion of obedient, implacable progress within the eternal seminary of WorkSpace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veni, Vida, Viva</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/07/27/veni-vida-viva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 14:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/07/27/veni-vida-viva/</guid>
      <description>Excerpt from PhD Dissertation by Barati Chand, Primary Azad Crawler team (Nodal Identification &amp;amp; Extrapolation [Kathmandu]).
Chand, B, 2069, &amp;ldquo;Anti-corporate Macro Phagocytosis in a Burgeoning Posthuman Context: The Scourge of Janahara&amp;rdquo; (unpublished PhD thesis), University of Kathmandu, Nepal.
Nodal Identification (NI) provides researchers with a critical tool-set to enable the location and examination of the pivotal spatial and cultural moments in an historical event. It is these nodal signifiers that substantively and essentially contribute to the temporal shape and flavour of a given moment, or set of events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Peasants Society</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/07/08/dead-peasants-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 21:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/07/08/dead-peasants-society/</guid>
      <description>WorkSpace has been called many things, a few of them complimentary. Bitter criticisms have been levelled, vain accusations made, torts brought, legal careers made and lost, even a few white collar lives sacrificed on the keen machete edge of corporate expansion. Despite the faint and diminishing mewling protests from a defanged Ofcorp, WorkSpace could never be accused of not adhering to most progressive, aggressive policies they could devise to ensure that they remained on the ragged edge of the corporate envelope expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moral Hazard</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/06/01/moral-hazard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 15:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/06/01/moral-hazard/</guid>
      <description>Week four in Fast Track started with the worst spring storm in twenty years. The tail end of hurricane Sheva, an anomalous El Nino child tempest, tore across the Atlantic in five days and smashed itself first against Ireland and then, barely diminished, romped across South West England into London. For once the faintly hysterical British approach to any weather outside of bucolic norms was justified. Heathrow was closed completely when an aging, fully fuelled, Boeing triple seven was pancaked by wind shear against a primary noise baffle outside Terminal 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orgone grinder</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/04/15/orgone-grinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 19:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/04/15/orgone-grinder/</guid>
      <description>WorkSpace Memo
Date stamp: 22-06-2028
Time (EST): 23:47
From the desk of Xiu Chen Wong; VP, Tech Overview for Job Maintenance (Europe)
To all Job Operators, (Implementation notification commencing 01-07-2028, 00:01):
Please Note: As of July 1, 2028 WorkSpace is dropping all support for the Job firmware OS based on the H4DAPI open source kernel. This decision is based on a number of factors, including:
 The growing need for a closed source, securable operating code for the Jobs Reduced WorkSpace tolerance for the undesirable personality memes still present in the open source community Proprietary requirements for an OS that can better manage organic overstretch implications of Confluence and other Total Employment activities  As such, your Job’s will shortly be receiving the appropriate system reformat and rebuild necessary for the deployment of the core code of WorkSpace HapLIS; this is a wholly internally derived and built code set, custom developed for the specialised requirements of WorkSpace All.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/04/05/stick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/04/05/stick/</guid>
      <description>Orientation, Section 3, subsection 3.4:
Fealty demonstrations:
WorkSpace employees (partners) herewith agree (ref, permalink: contractual obligation) to the following expression(s) of corporate allegiance to WorkSpace All. To wit:
3.4.1: Corpus support (CS):
as a new partner you are expected (ref, permalink: contractual obligation), to provide ad hoc and/or on-demand corporeal support to the corporation. This contribution will be at the absolute discretion of WorkSpace All, and may be exclusively interpreted ex parte (ref, p-link: WorkSpace Legal &amp;gt; partner glossary).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Over unity</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/03/19/gives-god-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 11:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/03/19/gives-god-head/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, Blue Shift, 23:00: Confluence hour.
Everyone does Confluence, the drones, the infrabeasts, even the management, even the brass. Parallel processing: new old-school – ponderous neurones and porridgy grey matter, the common muck of organics, always pluckily and inexplicably outdoing their carnal heritage.
The Examinds are the other half of the equation, the shiny future bit tugging their forelocks above the shockwave of the earthly light cone. Fuck knows what they think but for the time being they seem to be cooperating; SciSpace continually providing reassurances of their ongoing compliance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morality Gap</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/03/11/morality-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 12:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/03/11/morality-gap/</guid>
      <description>Abstraction is one of the main efficiency tools employed by WorkSpace. Their pet AIs have exhaustively evolved a number of strategems that ensure that any task, big or giga, can be pared down to a bland and abstract dataset for distributed processing.
Adopting a decentralised marquis cell structure but augmented with a pantopticon omniscience, WorkSpace ingeniously ensures efficient data processing, the risk reduction of corporate responsibility, and yet retains a full and robust capability for the individual recrimination of its component drones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job.</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/03/09/job/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 12:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/03/09/job/</guid>
      <description>Forget food pills, flying cars, everclean jumpsuits and moon holidays – what we got (if we’re lucky) was a Job.
They got some things right – cranial inputs and interface shunts, weakly omniscient AI, fully realised immersion environments: so fucking what. The dependency principle is ever present – data access, comfort, presence, credibility, fiscal viability: all predicated on the maintenance of a stream of fragile income. And at the mercy of a diminishing number of giga-nationals; like the autonomic twitching dermis of a dozing bovine, one errant spasm from these behemoths can snuff you out: PRESS 2 TO SPEAK TO OUR RECONNECTION TEAM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Machine</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/03/06/emotional-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 17:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/03/06/emotional-machine/</guid>
      <description>Dateline: 08/06/2026
 08:40
Today is the first day in my new Job, it arrives soon. The induction epack told me a courier was scheduled to arrive before nine.
09:13
The Job’s here. A big white domed shell made from industrial maize bespattered with a million logos and non-tamper user invalidation warnings. It wishes me a good morning and advises that I have two minutes to position it in my preferred location before it uses its executive override to decide for itself; it goes in the windowless backroom.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
