<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WorkSpace</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WorkSpace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&lt;Gabrielpost. closed broadcast|personal FB log.DATESTAMP: 12:47.12.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>/warped/2047-12-12-closed-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.47.12.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2047 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warped/2047-12-12-closed-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.47.12.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>Jonty was braver than most. He shucked his Primarni eight quid tunic and then only hesitated briefly before climbing into the cutter on his hands and knees. He snagged his Skin on a lower part of the chassis, a crappy weld I remember promising myself I&amp;rsquo;d dremel off and never did, scoring a painless weld on his shoulder. Under the harsh sodiums the Skin disappointed me as it always does. Despite the profound amount of technology crammed (nano-wise and micro-ways) into its 6mm dermis, it screamed Gov issue drab; they never did pin down the self-cleaning routines and dirt that wont wash away was tattooed into the gross creases under his shoulder blades and elbows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anonpost. general broadcast|backchannel.DATESTAMP: 12:13.12.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>/warped/2047-12-12-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.13.12.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2047 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warped/2047-12-12-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.13.12.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>Gabriel’s new rig was very different from the jointed, articulated octopi that most Cutter cells use. A columnar structure about 2.5 meters high with a central space just big enough for a person, close up it looked a little like a highly magnified section of squid tentacle, with countless very sharp hooks aligned in an endless spiroform. Later I find out that he took inspiration from ancient loopwheeler tech, a 20C weaving machine that outputted a seamless torso garment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anonpost. general broadcast|backchannel.DATESTAMP: 23:04.11.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-23.04.11.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2047 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-23.04.11.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>Stratford was delightful as always. I tried to turn left out of the station but my Skin forced an executive left into Great Eastern Road, tripling my walk time to Gabriel’s. There’s no way of knowing if I had just dodged a dirty bomb particulate cloud or if I was a tiny part of an evacuation modelling exercise, either way it was a ball ache. It was nearly 2300 by the time I got to the Village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anonpost. general broadcast|backchannel.DATESTAMP: 21:22.11.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-21.22.11.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2047 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-21.22.11.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>As normal the tube was late, the TerrorHurtz mid-tunnel scanners were always going on the fritz and the alert was pegged at Severe, this meant that the tube door secondary gait scanners were being extra-anal. As I entered the carriage I got a non-friendly spine tingle B-Aware ping; like all I’m going to do if I see a unattended package is huddle as close to it as possible – I cleave to the red-mist-is-better-than-triple-amputee mindset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anonpost. general broadcast|backchannel.DATESTAMP: 01:34.11.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-01.34.11.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2047 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-01.34.11.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>Going for the cut today. Fucking terrified. Gabriel’s got a new cutter setup in his basement, painstakingly assembled from gomied landfill and parts bought off a Chinese ebay clone. I’m the guinea pig and I’m shitting it. I can take the pain (morphine analogues nicked from Mum – de nada) but the bit that terrifies me is the damage (de-gloving, shudder) and the nudity. Not just the bare surface exposure, but the denuded lack, the comfort blanket removal that filled me with a lunar dread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapters</title>
      <link>/chapters.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 19:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chapters.html</guid>
      <description> The Deconstructed Man Ratchet Notes to Babs (#4) Notes to Babs (#12) It’s the only way to be sure Drip Down Critical Depth Nazca tweets Calvary soldier Brighton Run Deafblind date mute 97X1.BAM! Warped The Deal </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>warped</title>
      <link>/categories/warped.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 13:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/categories/warped.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;anonpost. general broadcast|backchannel.DATESTAMP: 01:34.11.12.47&amp;gt;
Going for the cut today. Fucking terrified. Gabriel’s got a new cutter setup in his basement, painstakingly assembled from gomied landfill and parts bought off a Chinese ebay clone. I’m the guinea pig and I’m shitting it. I can take the pain (morphine analogues nicked from Mum—de nada) but the bit that terrifies me is the damage (de-gloving, shudder) and the nudity. Not just the bare surface exposure, but the denuded lack, the comfort blanket removal that filled me with a lunar dread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Deal</title>
      <link>/2010/07/02/the-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 11:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/07/02/the-deal/</guid>
      <description>Shumi was flying. Save for a scarlet slash of cloth across her hips, she was naked and she didn’t care. With the certainty of dream knowledge she knew that bare skin was necessary to allow a seamless control of the air flow over her wings and body.
Turning her dream-tunnelled vision left and then right, she gazed at her wings—arching painlessly upwards, two pure silver impossible arcs propelled her wheeling progress above the endless, glittering scintilla of the Dhakan canalways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>97X-BAM!</title>
      <link>/2009/08/20/charlie-babbitt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 23:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/08/20/charlie-babbitt/</guid>
      <description>WorkSpace has the best PR. This should be no surprise as they also have the best of everything else; cherry picking was second nature to the myriad minds that ran the corporation. PR had to be good, they had the unenviable task of shoehorning an essentially incompatible prickly cactus cock of corporate reality into a sheath of barrier protection—there was no way that the public would allow the stark reality of WorkSpace realities into their lives without the blinkering cosmesis of spin to lube the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mute</title>
      <link>/2009/08/09/mute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 11:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/08/09/mute/</guid>
      <description>It lived in the sun. It thought with light. It was a tethered god. It is the largest living being on the planet.
From low earth orbit, perhaps 350 kilometres up, India is a stunning splinter of silver, a concentrated kernel of thermonuclear ur-light that whips around every ninety minutes, a man-made quasar in all but name. The National Solar Mission started in the 2010s was at the time the largest solar power initiative on the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deafblind date</title>
      <link>/2009/08/02/deafblind-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2009 15:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/08/02/deafblind-date/</guid>
      <description>Brant has travelled a bit, some contracting work in China, a stint in South America with a backpack and whining Danish girlfriend, even some Provencal pretensions as an abortive property developer (Brant couldn’t spot a bear market if it chewed his face off)—he flattered himself that he had evolved a keen eye for difference. Over the years he has developed what he privately calls an interpretation filter (his internal geek is inherently polysyllabic), the quality and successes of which he sees varying wildly from country to country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brighton Run</title>
      <link>/2009/07/11/brighton-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2009 11:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/07/11/brighton-run/</guid>
      <description>The liberti is called Daisy Longley. This fact (and several others) was delivered in a snivelly and hitched voice in between bouts of wretched crying in a Starbucks on Croydon High Street. Cradling a tall latte (extra hot, triple shot—her urban survival reflexes evidently still partially intact) and staring miserably into the middle distance, Daisy laboriously (and frankly after some time, boringly) relayed the events of the past hour.
Up until today, Daisy had been a dutiful member of HR at a WorkSpace subsidiary called The Prius Priest, a franchised hybrid vehicle-recycling centre situated just off the Purley Hill tram route.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calvary soldier</title>
      <link>/2009/07/02/calvary-soldier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 20:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/07/02/calvary-soldier/</guid>
      <description>Brant is out of child’s piss. This is a problem. A bigger one is getting more: avoiding the spastically reflexive anti-paedo screening, both passive bio and active thermograph (groin heat—see?), that typically encompasses the average suburban London school with a one and half kilometre perimeter of hand wringing anxiety is a non-viable approach for a white-skinned, sallow-cheeked skinhead in his mid-thirties. Even if you could get past last year’s grubby Addict (imagine the alternative though, a three year old suit—he would be on the nonce express to Pentonville before you could say &amp;lsquo;Madeline’s Law&amp;rsquo;), first avoiding a shiv from the sixth formers and then actually being able to meet the exorbitant price of the clean piss would exhaust both the bravery and the sketchy urban survival repertoire of a beleaguered WorkSpace worker with a diminishing handle on the daily mutating argot of anyone under the age of sixteen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nazca tweets</title>
      <link>/2009/05/31/nazca-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 14:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/05/31/nazca-tweets/</guid>
      <description>It could have gone either way. A haven-distributed, largely tax-free windfall of over two hundred and fifty million Euros can have a delirious effect on anyone. To a centless decon worker from the crushing fields of Chittagong it was initially mostly beyond comprehension.
A slightly more culture-saturated target of benefaction would have gone through the standard stages of lottery burn rate. By the 30s, LBR was an established, observable, behaviour meme—infinitesimally marginal lottery variants had been evolved and honed to maximise their pacification effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Critical Depth</title>
      <link>/2009/05/25/instruction-creep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 17:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/05/25/instruction-creep/</guid>
      <description>It turned out that saving the world was a bit of a let down, there was just so much crap to deal with. When he was at the Madhom yard (and when he had had the energy to think about it), it had seemed simple: Remove the bloatware management goons, up the base-level day rate by an order of magnitude, and decree a 5-day working week. Not without a substantial amount of irritation he learned the same lesson that a thousand previous owner/managers had learned the hard way: the hundred and one ills and wrongs committed by the management are just the poorly articulated output of a deeply imperfect machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drip Down</title>
      <link>/2009/05/19/drip-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 20:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/05/19/drip-down/</guid>
      <description>It is an article of faith at WorkSpace that at some point you’ll be told. Not because experience bears out this belief, and not because you believe that ultimately it is the right thing that should be done (check your quaint sensibilities at the front desk please), but merely because even in an organisation as paranoid and as demarcated as WorkSpace, the fabric of the place is porous. The walls have ears but they also have tongues—scabrous, rough, blunt proboscides that lap cat-like at the wispy fragments of information pervading from up above to down below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s the only way to be sure</title>
      <link>/2009/04/19/its-the-only-way-to-be-sure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 15:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/04/19/its-the-only-way-to-be-sure/</guid>
      <description>At nearly thirty-seven thousand kilometres above southern Afghanistan, the geo-stationary WorkSpace relay milsat is a barely detectable stellar mote in the clear, frigid, night sky. Suspended in a cylindrical vat of liquid helium, and protected with a ring of bulky tanks of propellant, the mind of the satellite pulses gently with a superconductive glow. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t really think, WorkSpace tends to impose a strict AI capacity cap on geosynchronous weapons platforms with kinetic missile capability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes to Babs (#4)</title>
      <link>/2009/04/19/notes-to-babs-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/04/19/notes-to-babs-4/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s hard Babs. Being human I mean; most days I wish I was like you. A synthetic, mediated consciousness devoid of anxiety, fear, self doubt, and pointless introspection. Today was horrible—don&amp;rsquo;t sigh, I know I say that most days—but honestly, you have no idea (can have no idea) about the near bottomless capacity of crassness that you have plugged me into. Take small talk for example, I mean come on—don&amp;rsquo;t these people even attempt some degree of output filtering?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes to Babs (#12)</title>
      <link>/2009/04/19/work-makes-you-free-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 12:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/04/19/work-makes-you-free-2/</guid>
      <description>Screen burn, carpet wear
Voice mail hell: Press Star then Hash
Thank fuck for vodka</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visitor&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>/visitors-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 21:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/visitors-guide/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are reading this at my industrial tribunal, as a data archaeologist student, or as drone level sysadmin clearing space off a grandfathered WorkSpace database, I hope it brings you some small distraction from the otherwise humdrum irritations of your work day.
This is deep backchannel, as far as I can tell no one has broken my crypto yet – my analytics show zero – so the photons striking whatever passes for eyes where you’re at are conveying bona fide, grass roots, uncensored serf level worker angst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratchet</title>
      <link>/2009/03/08/ratchet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 13:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/03/08/ratchet/</guid>
      <description>Even with the pharmacological mitigation and enclosure comfort provided by the Job, therapy with my patients rarely shared the structured, ethereal angst of a first world counselling session. Dealing not with the maybe, the bogeymen of possibility, the faint spectre of disaster—all distant cousins to true pain; these fragmented souls had already seen and felt far too much real trauma to compare even fleetingly with my pampered albionside client base. After a year of patching up tattered psyches, gibbering will-o-the-wisp surgery survivors, I have developed an involuntary rage response when I think back to the work I did at my Acton practise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Deconstructed Man</title>
      <link>/2009/02/25/the-deconstructed-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 21:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/02/25/the-deconstructed-man/</guid>
      <description>The activated charcoal in the aircon had long since been active and the prefab smelled like camping trips and the drying wetsuit tang of childhood seaside visits. I pegged back the membrane door as far as it could go and we all shuffled in. Zalmai brought up the rear, taxiing reluctantly into the musty space. Currently our complement is only seven, a recent c.difficile outbreak resulted in two deaths—only one surprise, a goat farmer who wandered into the hospital compound unaided, only missing a lung and his left hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empennage</title>
      <link>/2009/02/24/empennage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 19:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/02/24/empennage/</guid>
      <description>Air quality permitting I try and hold the group sessions outside. When the particulate meter settles into a quasi-quiescent tick-tock metronome, we bundle up the patients into hand-me-down NBCs and stretcher/carry/cajole our charges into the ambulance (an ungainly USMC anti-mine deuce and a half) and head south-east to the poppy fields near the Khyber Pass. Since the mujahideen went synthetic savvy and the UNODC quashed production with the simple expedience of tactical nukes, the endless opium plantations have gone to seed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out patient</title>
      <link>/2009/02/10/out-patient/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 22:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/02/10/out-patient/</guid>
      <description>13th January 2031
There is a certain weary comfort to a Monday morning here; despite the horrors in the prefabs and the faintly gamma-positive sleet pocking the poly roof of my office, I take some solace from the generic, familiar schlep of the starting week.
I had been up for three hours already, a nagging occipitalis ache dragging me neck-first from an uneasy sleep on my surplus noncom cot. In contrast to my usual fractious, broken dreams, my office looked the same as always: a small pokey appendix epoxied to the back of the main ward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What it&#39;s like not to believe</title>
      <link>/2008/10/21/what-its-like-not-to-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 21:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/10/21/what-its-like-not-to-believe/</guid>
      <description>Deep down in the WorkSpace corporate lexicon, somewhere between WashWord (ref: outbound content checks), and Weasel (mid management slang: derogatory) is: WASTE. Terminologies rated corporate pivotal (i.e.: relating to criteria rated indistinguishable from the basic genetics of the WorkSpace raison d’etre) are always fully textually capitalised, and are mandated to remain so always. WASTE (implying a keen imperative to avoid profligacy) is one of the big three, one third of the corporate triadic indivisible from the notion of obedient, implacable progress within the eternal seminary of WorkSpace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pathology</title>
      <link>/2008/08/31/pathology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 14:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/08/31/pathology/</guid>
      <description>It didn’t look like a corpse, but he was very dead. Dead bodies are pitiful; a triple amputee cadaver the colour of dirty pond ice is utterly pathetic, a roadkill would have had more pathos. Devoid of the mobilising energy that used this substandard shell in life, the truncated body was a palimpsest of a lifetime of self harm and useless delusion. Crippled by a dysfunctional endocrine system and a cranky neurochemistry, and bolstered by decades of supposed and imagined derision, this man had wilfully and incrementally reduced his body to a torso and one over-muscled left arm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bullpup</title>
      <link>/2008/07/31/bullpup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 20:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/07/31/bullpup/</guid>
      <description>Tad, like all mid-management predators, has always viewed the notion of legality as just another commercial variable to be negotiated. Legal and morality considerations, however vestigial, and when favourably ignorable, are eliminated via a rigorous internal MBA top-up during the first six months of WorkSpace employment. Tad is as comfortable with Antarctic carbon-dumping cost benefit analysis as he is with bland revenue projections for PlaySpace, the stark WorkSpace crèche facility maintained at the Gaunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veni, Vida, Viva</title>
      <link>/2008/07/27/veni-vida-viva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 14:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/07/27/veni-vida-viva/</guid>
      <description>Excerpt from PhD Dissertation by Barati Chand, Primary Azad Crawler team (Nodal Identification &amp;amp; Extrapolation [Kathmandu]):
Chand, B, 2069, &amp;ldquo;Anti-corporate Macro Phagocytosis in a Burgeoning Posthuman Context: The Scourge of Janahara&amp;rdquo; (unpublished PhD thesis), University of Kathmandu, Nepal.
Nodal Identification (NI) provides researchers with a critical tool-set to enable the location and examination of the pivotal spatial and cultural moments in an historical event. It is these nodal signifiers that substantively and essentially contribute to the temporal shape and flavour of a given moment, or set of events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It rubs the lotion on its skin</title>
      <link>/2008/07/10/it-rubs-the-lotion-on-its-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/07/10/it-rubs-the-lotion-on-its-skin/</guid>
      <description>Remarkable is discouraged. Excellent is frowned upon. Deviance, though, in typical WorkSpace narrow focus, is lauded.
Tad Revert is not remarkable, not these days. In the noise and soup of moral ambiguity that defines the trencher of middle management scrap squabbles, he barely rates above norm for aberrant deviancy. Plucked from the thousands of job applicants to hit WorkSpace servers on an hourly basis, Tad was short listed for a management role seventeen seconds after hitting send in his mail client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Peasants Society</title>
      <link>/2008/07/08/dead-peasants-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 21:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/07/08/dead-peasants-society/</guid>
      <description>WorkSpace has been called many things, a few of them complimentary. Bitter criticisms have been levelled, vain accusations made, torts brought, legal careers made and lost, even a few white collar lives sacrificed on the keen machete edge of corporate expansion. Despite the faint and diminishing mewling protests from a defanged Ofcorp, WorkSpace could never be accused of not adhering to most progressive, aggressive policies they could devise to ensure that they remained on the ragged edge of the corporate envelope expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bellend X-1</title>
      <link>/2008/06/17/bellend-x-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 13:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/06/17/bellend-x-1/</guid>
      <description>Monday 07:47
Gecko I ain’t.
I’ve been shitting myself since Babs yanked me out of deep REM at five-thirty; not meanly though—no intrathecal microvoltage, Babs has chilled out considerably since the flush has faded from his post-upgrade zeal. His/her newly emergent, more rounded persona is quite agreeable as well, convincingly androgynous (s)he skirts expertly, and eerily, the base level gender determinant that underpins any organic relationship building. Basically (s)he has removed the one major potential divisive element in our new relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hastati la Vista</title>
      <link>/2008/06/15/hastati-la-vista/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 15:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/06/15/hastati-la-vista/</guid>
      <description>Fast Track is over; apparently I’m a manager now. No epiphanic transformation has occurred, no Damascian de-scaling; perhaps I’m missing some critical genetic component that permits the phase change into ideal mid-management material. So, again, I’m faking it; firstly as a drone-level faux-featly specialist, and now, more holistically, as an embedded, larval agent. Daily I am amazed at the duplicity of my existence, thoroughly compartmentalizing two completely divergent mindsets, one bent on psychological maintenance, the other on the more prosaic physical continuity of survival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moral Hazard</title>
      <link>/2008/06/01/moral-hazard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 15:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/06/01/moral-hazard/</guid>
      <description>Week four in Fast Track started with the worst spring storm in twenty years. The tail end of hurricane Sheva, an anomalous El Nino child tempest, tore across the Atlantic in five days and smashed itself first against Ireland and then, barely diminished, romped across South West England into London. For once the faintly hysterical British approach to any weather outside of bucolic norms was justified. Heathrow was closed completely when an aging, fully fuelled, Boeing triple seven was pancaked by wind shear against a primary noise baffle outside Terminal 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piebald Piper</title>
      <link>/2008/05/26/piebald-piper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 14:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/26/piebald-piper/</guid>
      <description>It’s been six months since He came to live in my head.
I was born deaf, an unfortunate genetic confluence called Waardenburg syndrome determined that I would never hear and never speak like you. I can talk after a fashion but the guttural qualities of my voice test the cursory patience of all but a few of the people I meet. I look a little odd too, not fairground grotesque but weird enough for most people to duck their heads or cross the road when I go out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acclimation</title>
      <link>/2008/05/25/acclimation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 16:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/25/acclimation/</guid>
      <description>Agate thought she had adequately prepared for not working. For the past thirteen months she had been subsistence level living; no booze, no new media, base spec nourishment, she had even become an amateur seamstress: she had saved over a hundred thousand euros. Pre-resignation this had seemed like a huge amount, a chunky hedge against poverty and the hydra grasp of a taxation system seemingly designed to obviate all disposable income and still allow stinking piles of garbage to build up monthly on Leyton road where Agate rented her small apartment in the old Olympic village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posthuman orphan</title>
      <link>/2008/05/18/posthuman-orphan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 12:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/18/posthuman-orphan/</guid>
      <description>Fast Track: Week 2; Day 2.
What a terrible fucking day. Someone died in class. We were half way through &amp;ldquo;Redistribution of Economic Profit Zones: Sino-Consumption Trends&amp;rdquo;, when it happened. I had only got to know Rhiain a little over the past week or so, she was a small, quiet, slight Welsh girl with a lilting accent, only slightly dulled by WorkSpace vernacular and three years of living in Hackney.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti-ethics</title>
      <link>/2008/05/14/anti-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 21:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/14/anti-ethics/</guid>
      <description>Fast Track: Day 3.
&amp;ldquo;Our envy of others devours us most of all.&amp;rdquo;
This cheery Power Point statement greets us at 08:01; only WorkSpace could subvert a gloomy Solzhenityism into a management training slide show. After two days of this crushing shit I can only assume that this pithy call to arms is going to form the policy core of yet another exercise in share holder value enhancement credo. The official title of the day’s module is (deep breath):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This way to the egress</title>
      <link>/2008/05/11/this-way-to-the-egress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/11/this-way-to-the-egress/</guid>
      <description>The softly glowing virch pointer hovers for a long moment over the Send icon, then, with an involuntary anal clench she fiercely toggles the command.
Recipient: hr@workspace.co.uk
Subject: Notice of resignation
Importance: High
&amp;hellip;Message sent
She tears off the goggles with trembling hands, she hasn’t bothered to fully dunk to send the message; this morning, given her terminal intentions, she hadn’t considered it worthwhile prepping for full immersion.
The response, whilst not instantaneous (machine intelligence has to find time to interface with its tardy human counterparts), is violently swift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motherless child</title>
      <link>/2008/05/01/motherless-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 18:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/01/motherless-child/</guid>
      <description>From: dohna.kanti@thdl.org.np
To: hadast@haifa.ac.lb
Cc:
Subject: Here’s the opportunity, let’s not linger…
Sent: Wed, 26,September, 2068
Dear Hadas,
Just thought I would drop you a line, BIG news. It’s been a while anyway since we last corresponded and you know how I hate meeting in the World, a technophobe to the end I suppose.
Anyway, my work on the Azad project goes well; as well it should after three years of research in six cities and two year-long Lorbital sabbaticals (much praise to my crawler team as well of course, and the admin here at Lhasa is a genius with partials management, and naturally we all love the bots).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your name’s not down</title>
      <link>/2008/04/29/your-names-not-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 20:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/29/your-names-not-down/</guid>
      <description>In his short and largely cheerless life, Janahara has lacked a great many things; regular nourishment, more than one set of clothes, a semblance of health care, reliably potable water—to name a few. Latterly though, he’s realising just quite how thoroughly fucked over he’s been. Time itself, it seems, like all luxuries, is also the preserve of those already benefiting from an existing level of corporeal comfort. A myopic fixation on the scant privations of hand-to-mouth existence does not allow choice, let alone an appreciation of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No space, man</title>
      <link>/2008/04/28/no-space-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 18:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/28/no-space-man/</guid>
      <description>After years of brute demolition, basic rending and tearing, Janahara’s team is learning for the first time (unwillingly but quickly) the art of incremental, non-destructive deconstruction.
The briefing (another weird new concept) in the management compound at Madhom had a core message: fuck up the decon and there would be no bonus. It turns out that reducing an International Space Station life support module (now Iqbal’s casual, urbane reference to the ISS becomes clear) to its component, fiscally useful, parts and materials was no cake walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noman</title>
      <link>/2008/04/27/noman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 14:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/27/noman/</guid>
      <description>Janahara hates it when his boss visits; he sees it as a fundamental breach of the uneven covenant between boss and crew. Stay out of sight you rich fucks.
Laughably called the crew lounge (a notional, nearly derisory, nod to UNEP recommendations), Kashem Corp provides one small, sixteen square metre plywood break time shack. This is perched on the boundary between the scrubby Chittagong shoreline and the endless mud flats at the seaward entrance to the main Madhom breaking yard; the crews call it, in a rare display of fatigue-tinged irony, the HQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisyphus rising</title>
      <link>/2008/04/26/sisyphus-rising/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 17:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/26/sisyphus-rising/</guid>
      <description>Janahara Azad hates his job, his boss, and his exo-suit, in that order. The first is unavoidable, the second repellent, and the third tetchy, recalcitrant and intermittently cooperative.
Three hours into an 18 hour shift: Madhom Bibir Hat averages 98% humidity, 42 Celsius, mercilessly lit by a diffuse sun which glints dully off the eternal mud. On the outskirts of the breaking yard itself, and for all the surrealism of the monstrous dead tech littering the landscape and the insane levels of activity in the main yard, it is a curiously peaceful place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going forward</title>
      <link>/2008/04/23/going-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 22:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/23/going-forward/</guid>
      <description>WorkSpace boasts a &amp;ldquo;rigorous selection process&amp;rdquo; in their corporate literature. No fucking shit. I am sure that the nervous troupe of newb managers that tottered through the titanium portals of WorkSpace HQ (RL) thought that after a week long interview process their positions would be secure. Yeah, right. Twelve of us pass through the proscribed materials TerrorHurtz detector tunnel in single file; nine come out of the other end into the vast lobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Defiant One</title>
      <link>/2008/04/23/the-defiant-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 11:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/23/the-defiant-one/</guid>
      <description>I don’t often get to see 05:30; thanks to Babs, early rises are now, not a normal part, but at least a regular part of what passes for my life these days.
My WorkSpace mandated morning regimen is delightful. A 90-second shower, maximum permitted temperature: 40 Celsius. Oatmeal: tepid. Coffee: decaf. Enjoyment: proscribed. I’m being overly harsh I’m sure; there are upsides: Clean clothes, a fading suit rash, no catheter, fresh-fuckin-air, epic bandwidth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centralia</title>
      <link>/2008/04/20/centralia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2008 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/20/centralia/</guid>
      <description>Re: ASE Providence tower report (Blackheath) &amp;ldquo;Surveillance Tower 4, East&amp;rdquo;
From: ase_prov4E@ministryofjustice.org
Date: 2028-07-05, 16:39:27
To: WorkSpace Operator Monitoring (UK) Alejandro_fernandez@workspace.world
Surveillance summary report
Author: Tower 4, AI agent child (sentience rated: 0.63, non-intuitive)
Subject: WorkSpace employee (London Operators, teams 4-11) team building sessions
Location: Blackheath neo-gambrel leisure biome (SE3)
Date stamp: 2028-07-04
Report focus: Atypical employee behaviour (Filter: Known downtime anti-social conduct variants)
A.M. Session (start time: 07:30, end time: 11:45)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quizling</title>
      <link>/2008/04/17/quizling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 20:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/17/quizling/</guid>
      <description>There are five of them, all faceless, arrayed behind a bland blonde wood table. They must have applied some sort of management witchcraft review hack to my ocular feed; the rest of the office remains crystal, rendered, clear; but whenever I try to focus on their faces I get macula fuzz-out and a stab of pain in both eyes. Nice touch, even face to face, management interactions are a one-way info transaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyperunreal</title>
      <link>/2008/04/16/hyperunreal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 21:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/16/hyperunreal/</guid>
      <description>I’ve never been to WorkSpace Prime (Tier 2) before, and frankly, it’s fucking weird. And not weird in a weird way; it’s just too normal.
We all do it, winding ourselves up daily with pocket fantasies about how Management are revelling in the glut of resource and matérial that their privilege brings; in our mind’s eye we see them rorting and cavorting in shift-less freedom like a Vegas winner cliché on a bed of paper money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orgone grinder</title>
      <link>/2008/04/15/orgone-grinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 19:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/15/orgone-grinder/</guid>
      <description>WorkSpace Memo
Date stamp: 22-06-2028
Time (EST): 23:47
From the desk of Xiu Chen Wong; VP, Tech Overview for Job Maintenance (Europe)
To all Job Operators, (Implementation notification commencing 01-07-2028, 00:01):
Please Note: As of July 1, 2028 WorkSpace is dropping all support for the Job firmware OS based on the H4DAPI open source kernel. This decision is based on a number of factors, including:
The growing need for a closed source, securable operating code for the Jobs Reduced WorkSpace tolerance for the undesirable personality memes still present in the open source community Proprietary requirements for an OS that can better manage organic overstretch implications of Confluence and other Total Employment activities As such, your Job’s will shortly be receiving the appropriate system reformat and rebuild necessary for the deployment of the core code of WorkSpace HapLIS; this is a wholly internally derived and built code set, custom developed for the specialised requirements of WorkSpace All.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bullet point time</title>
      <link>/2008/04/09/bullet-point-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 18:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/09/bullet-point-time/</guid>
      <description>The cell wall fills my entire view, the membrane soaring gelatinously towards the notional roof of the Tank. 10,000 seconds in full virch schlepping my way through several TB of endoplasmic reconfig—basically fixing someone else’s sloppy code. The client is waiting and I’m suffering hard with the basic incompatibility of overdue deadline with Monday morning apathy.
WTF—the Tank construct stutters, then freezes completely. Un-fucking-heard of. Like an old movie from the Sci-Fi Classics channel the entire space looks like it’s been embedded in a crystalline block, even the Prims just hover mid-mod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week end</title>
      <link>/2008/04/06/weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/06/weekend/</guid>
      <description>Friday always hurts. Divestment is a bitch; Job does its best, a mild pre-exmmersion palliative analgesic plus some standard reality counselling hypnotics, but still, RL is always a grind at first. Gravity reasserts, data access is torturously slow, cooking—sheesh, and the sheer effort of having to interact on the poverty of the human-only level.
Coarse lumpen humanity everywhere you look. Brains, mouths and tongues forming (so slowly), the info-poor commerce on the pitifully narrow organic bandwidth that is people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick</title>
      <link>/2008/04/05/stick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/05/stick/</guid>
      <description>Orientation, Section 3, subsection 3.4:
Fealty demonstrations:
WorkSpace employees (partners) herewith agree (ref, permalink: contractual obligation) to the following expression(s) of corporate allegiance to WorkSpace All. To wit:
3.4.1: Corpus support (CS):
as a new partner you are expected (ref, permalink: contractual obligation), to provide ad hoc and/or on-demand corporeal support to the corporation. This contribution will be at the absolute discretion of WorkSpace All, and may be exclusively interpreted ex parte (ref, p-link: WorkSpace Legal &amp;gt; partner glossary).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Over unity</title>
      <link>/2008/03/19/gives-god-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 11:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/03/19/gives-god-head/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, Blue Shift, 23:00: Confluence hour.
Everyone does Confluence, the drones, the infrabeasts, even the management, even the brass. Parallel processing: new old-school—ponderous neurones and porridgy grey matter, the common muck of organics, always pluckily and inexplicably outdoing their carnal heritage.
The Examinds are the other half of the equation, the shiny future bit tugging their forelocks above the shockwave of the earthly light cone. Fuck knows what they think but for the time being they seem to be cooperating; SciSpace continually providing reassurances of their ongoing compliance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rez</title>
      <link>/2008/03/18/rez/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 18:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/03/18/rez/</guid>
      <description>Magic or Alcor?
Non-denominational;
I want a big egg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Null cipher</title>
      <link>/2008/03/16/null-cipher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 14:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/03/16/null-cipher/</guid>
      <description>I’m not going to tell you my name.
That’s SOP I’m afraid for your average WorkSpace employee; constant surveillance tends to breed a certain phobic reaction to divulging personal information unnecessarily. This reticence has a certain pitiful bravado about it; ethnographers early last decade first noticed this trend towards self-censorship on the lowest corporate rungs. Call centre staff in the double oughts, while exposed to the full merciless blast of the futile howling public, instinctively and rapidly learned the power of true names; the substitution of &amp;ldquo;Operator #MT128&amp;rdquo; or similar became commonplace—the only privacy bastion (savagely protected) left in a terminally denuded workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morality Gap</title>
      <link>/2008/03/11/morality-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 12:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/03/11/morality-gap/</guid>
      <description>Abstraction is one of the main efficiency tools employed by WorkSpace. Their pet AIs have exhaustively evolved a number of strategems that ensure that any task, big or giga, can be pared down to a bland and abstract dataset for distributed processing.
Adopting a decentralised marquis cell structure but augmented with a pantopticon omniscience, WorkSpace ingeniously ensures efficient data processing, the risk reduction of corporate responsibility, and yet retains a full and robust capability for the individual recrimination of its component drones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job.</title>
      <link>/2008/03/09/job/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 12:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/03/09/job/</guid>
      <description>Forget food pills, flying cars, everclean jumpsuits and moon holidays—what we got (if we’re lucky) was a Job.
They got some things right—cranial inputs and interface shunts, weakly omniscient AI, fully realised immersion environments: so fucking what. The dependency principle is ever present—data access, comfort, presence, credibility, fiscal viability: all predicated on the maintenance of a stream of fragile income. And at the mercy of a diminishing number of giga-nationals; like the autonomic twitching dermis of a dozing bovine, one errant spasm from these behemoths can snuff you out: PRESS 2 TO SPEAK TO OUR RECONNECTION TEAM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-binding Agreement</title>
      <link>/2008/03/08/non-binding-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 12:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/03/08/non-binding-agreement/</guid>
      <description>DownTime overlays as my clock rolls past 16k seconds. The haematic assay has determined that a rest period is appropriate, Babs initiates the shunt.
A curt text horiscroll rudely bumps the load screen though: &amp;ldquo;Mandatory KPI overview scheduled in 3200 seconds, please ensure dunk readiness to facilitate prompt processing&amp;rdquo;.
I sigh inwardly (my control over autonomic displays of physical frustration is long practised and nothing gets through the loyalty buffer); I suppose it had to happen sooner or later, nearly two weeks in with new Job and no direct avatime yet with management—I was going to have to justify my existence to the man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Machine</title>
      <link>/2008/03/06/emotional-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 17:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/03/06/emotional-machine/</guid>
      <description>Dateline: 08/06/2026
08:40
Today is the first day in my new Job, it arrives soon. The induction epack told me a courier was scheduled to arrive before nine.
09:13
The Job’s here. A big white domed shell made from industrial maize bespattered with a million logos and non-tamper user invalidation warnings. It wishes me a good morning and advises that I have two minutes to position it in my preferred location before it uses its executive override to decide for itself; it goes in the windowless backroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anotatepost. closed broadcast|personal FB log.NO DATESTAMP&gt;</title>
      <link>/warped/1970-01-01-closed-broadcast-personal-fb-log.no-datestamp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warped/1970-01-01-closed-broadcast-personal-fb-log.no-datestamp.html</guid>
      <description>Social historians looking back at the middle of 21C will perhaps puzzle at the predominance of starkly non-expressive faces in images or video captured in public places. As surveillance saturation increased from the early 2010s onwards, fuelled by ever granular taxing methods and notional terrorism threats, the general populace evolved means of reducing their biometric footprint. Gait modification trusses were at first home-brewed and then Chinese mass produced. After hoodies were outlawed grass roots lecture sessions on how to fool facial recognition software grew in popularity, and sign language jumped the gap from prosthesis to de facto language.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
