<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Warpeds on WorkSpace</title>
    <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Warpeds on WorkSpace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2047 12:47:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&lt;Gabrielpost. closed broadcast|personal FB log.DATESTAMP: 12:47.12.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-12-closed-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.47.12.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2047 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-12-closed-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.47.12.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>Jonty was braver than most. He shucked his Primarni eight quid tunic and then only hesitated briefly before climbing into the cutter on his hands and knees. He snagged his Skin on a lower part of the chassis, a crappy weld I remember promising myself I&amp;rsquo;d dremel off and never did, scoring a painless weld on his shoulder. Under the harsh sodiums the Skin disappointed me as it always does. Despite the profound amount of technology crammed (nano-wise and micro-ways) into its 6mm dermis, it screamed Gov issue drab; they never did pin down the self-cleaning routines and dirt that wont wash away was tattooed into the gross creases under his shoulder blades and elbows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anonpost. general broadcast|backchannel.DATESTAMP: 12:13.12.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-12-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.13.12.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2047 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-12-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.13.12.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>Gabriel’s new rig was very different from the jointed, articulated octopi that most Cutter cells use. A columnar structure about 2.5 meters high with a central space just big enough for a person, close up it looked a little like a highly magnified section of squid tentacle, with countless very sharp hooks aligned in an endless spiroform. Later I find out that he took inspiration from ancient loopwheeler tech, a 20C weaving machine that outputted a seamless torso garment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anonpost. general broadcast|backchannel.DATESTAMP: 23:04.11.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-23.04.11.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2047 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-23.04.11.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>Stratford was delightful as always. I tried to turn left out of the station but my Skin forced an executive left into Great Eastern Road, tripling my walk time to Gabriel’s. There’s no way of knowing if I had just dodged a dirty bomb particulate cloud or if I was a tiny part of an evacuation modelling exercise, either way it was a ball ache. It was nearly 2300 by the time I got to the Village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anonpost. general broadcast|backchannel.DATESTAMP: 21:22.11.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-21.22.11.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2047 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-21.22.11.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>As normal the tube was late, the TerrorHurtz mid-tunnel scanners were always going on the fritz and the alert was pegged at Severe, this meant that the tube door secondary gait scanners were being extra-anal. As I entered the carriage I got a non-friendly spine tingle B-Aware ping; like all I’m going to do if I see a unattended package is huddle as close to it as possible – I cleave to the red-mist-is-better-than-triple-amputee mindset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anonpost. general broadcast|backchannel.DATESTAMP: 01:34.11.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-01.34.11.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2047 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/2047-12-11-general-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-01.34.11.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>Going for the cut today. Fucking terrified. Gabriel’s got a new cutter setup in his basement, painstakingly assembled from gomied landfill and parts bought off a Chinese ebay clone. I’m the guinea pig and I’m shitting it. I can take the pain (morphine analogues nicked from Mum – de nada) but the bit that terrifies me is the damage (de-gloving, shudder) and the nudity. Not just the bare surface exposure, but the denuded lack, the comfort blanket removal that filled me with a lunar dread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anotatepost. closed broadcast|personal FB log.NO DATESTAMP&gt;</title>
      <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/1970-01-01-closed-broadcast-personal-fb-log.no-datestamp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/warped/1970-01-01-closed-broadcast-personal-fb-log.no-datestamp.html</guid>
      <description>Social historians looking back at the middle of 21C will perhaps puzzle at the predominance of starkly non-expressive faces in images or video captured in public places. As surveillance saturation increased from the early 2010s onwards, fuelled by ever granular taxing methods and notional terrorism threats, the general populace evolved means of reducing their biometric footprint. Gait modification trusses were at first home-brewed and then Chinese mass produced. After hoodies were outlawed grass roots lecture sessions on how to fool facial recognition software grew in popularity, and sign language jumped the gap from prosthesis to de facto language.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
