<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Janahara on WorkSpace</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/janahara/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Janahara on WorkSpace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 11:39:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/janahara/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Deal</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2010/07/02/the-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 11:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2010/07/02/the-deal/</guid>
      <description>Shumi was flying. Save for a scarlet slash of cloth across her hips, she was naked and she didn’t care. With the certainty of dream knowledge she knew that bare skin was necessary to allow a seamless control of the air flow over her wings and body. Turning her dream-tunnelled vision left and then right she gazed at her wings – arching painlessly upwards, two pure silver impossible arcs propelled her effortless, wheeling progress above the endless, glittering scintilla of the Dhakan canalways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nazca tweets</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/05/31/nazca-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 14:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/05/31/nazca-tweets/</guid>
      <description>It could have gone either way. A haven-distributed, largely tax-free windfall of over two hundred and fifty million Euros can have a delirious effect on anyone. To a centless decon worker from the crushing fields of Chittagong it was initially mostly beyond comprehension. A slightly more culture saturated target of benefaction would have gone through the standard stages of lottery burn rate. By the 30s LBR was an established, observable, behaviour meme – infinitesimally marginal lottery variants had been evolved and honed to maximise their pacification effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Critical Depth</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/05/25/instruction-creep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 17:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/05/25/instruction-creep/</guid>
      <description>It turned out that saving the world was a bit of a let down, there was just so much crap to deal with. When he was at the Madhom yard (and when he had had the energy to think about it), it had seemed simple: Remove the bloatware management goons, up the base-level day rate by an order of magnitude and decree a 5-day working week. Not without a substantial amount of irritation he learned the same lesson that a thousand previous owner/managers had learned the hard way – the hundred and one ills and wrongs committed by the management are just the poorly articulated output of a deeply imperfect machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motherless child</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/05/01/motherless-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 18:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/05/01/motherless-child/</guid>
      <description>From: dohna.kanti@thdl.org.np
To: hadast@haifa.ac.lb
Cc:
Subject: Here’s the opportunity, let’s not linger…
Sent: Wed, 26,September, 2068
Dear Hadas,
Just thought I would drop you a line, BIG news. It’s been a while anyway since we last corresponded and you know how I hate meeting in the World, a technophobe to the end I suppose. Anyway, my work on the Azad project goes well; as well it should after three years of research in six cities and two year-long Lorbital sabbaticals (much praise to my crawler team as well of course, and the admin here at Lhasa is a genius with partials management, and naturally we all love the bots).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your name’s not down</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/04/29/your-names-not-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 20:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/04/29/your-names-not-down/</guid>
      <description>In his short and largely cheerless life, Janahara has lacked a great many things; regular nourishment, more than one set of clothes, a semblance of health care, reliably potable water – to name a few. Latterly though, he’s realising just quite how thoroughly fucked over he’s been. Time itself, it seems, like all luxuries, is also the preserve of those already benefiting from an existing level of corporeal comfort. A myopic fixation on the scant privations of hand to mouth existence does not allow choice, let alone an appreciation of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No space, man</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/04/28/no-space-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 18:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/04/28/no-space-man/</guid>
      <description>After years of brute demolition, basic rending and tearing, Janahara’s team is learning for the first time (unwillingly but quickly) the art of incremental, non-destructive deconstruction.
The briefing (another weird new concept) in the management compound at Madhom had a core message: fuck up the decon and there would be no bonus. It turns out that reducing an International Space Station life support module (now Iqbal’s casual, urbane reference to the ISS becomes clear) to its component, fiscally useful, parts and materials was no cake walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noman</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/04/27/noman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 14:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/04/27/noman/</guid>
      <description>Janahara hates it when his boss visits; he sees it as a fundamental breach of the uneven covenant between boss and crew. Stay out of sight you rich fucks.
Laughably called the crew lounge (a notional, nearly derisory, nod to UNEP recommendations), Kashem Corp provides one small, sixteen square metre plywood break time shack. This is perched on the boundary between the scrubby Chittagong shoreline and the endless mud flats at the seaward entrance to the main Madhom breaking yard; the crews call it, in a rare display of fatigue tinged irony, the HQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisyphus rising</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/04/26/sisyphus-rising/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 17:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/04/26/sisyphus-rising/</guid>
      <description>Janahara Azad hates his job, his boss, and his exo-suit, in that order. The first is unavoidable, the second repellent, and the third tetchy, recalcitrant and intermittently cooperative.
Three hours into an 18 hour shift: Madhom Bibir Hat averages 98% humidity, 42 Celsius, mercilessly lit by a diffuse sun which glints dully off the eternal mud. On the outskirts of the breaking yard itself, and for all the surrealism of the monstrous dead tech littering the landscape and the insane levels of activity in the main yard, it is a curiously peaceful place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
