<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tad Revert on WorkSpace</title>
    <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/categories/tad-revert.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tad Revert on WorkSpace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 20:27:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/categories/tad-revert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bullpup</title>
      <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/2008/07/31/bullpup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 20:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/2008/07/31/bullpup/</guid>
      <description>Tad, like all mid-management predators, has always viewed the notion of legality as just another commercial variable to be negotiated. Legal and morality considerations, however vestigial, and when favourably ignorable, are eliminated via a rigorous internal MBA top-up during the first six months of WorkSpace employment. Tad is as comfortable with Antarctic carbon-dumping cost benefit analysis as he is with bland revenue projections for PlaySpace, the stark WorkSpace crèche facility maintained at the Gaunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It rubs the lotion on its skin</title>
      <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/2008/07/10/it-rubs-the-lotion-on-its-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/2008/07/10/it-rubs-the-lotion-on-its-skin/</guid>
      <description>Remarkable is discouraged. Excellent is frowned upon. Deviance, though, in typical WorkSpace narrow focus, is lauded.
Tad Revert is not remarkable, not these days. In the noise and soup of moral ambiguity that defines the trencher of middle management scrap squabbles, he barely rates above norm for aberrant deviancy. Plucked from the thousands of job applicants to hit WorkSpace servers on an hourly basis, Tad was short listed for a management role seventeen seconds after hitting send in his mail client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Peasants Society</title>
      <link>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/2008/07/08/dead-peasants-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 21:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mythaxis.github.io/WorkSpace/2008/07/08/dead-peasants-society/</guid>
      <description>WorkSpace has been called many things, a few of them complimentary. Bitter criticisms have been levelled, vain accusations made, torts brought, legal careers made and lost, even a few white collar lives sacrificed on the keen machete edge of corporate expansion. Despite the faint and diminishing mewling protests from a defanged Ofcorp, WorkSpace could never be accused of not adhering to most progressive, aggressive policies they could devise to ensure that they remained on the ragged edge of the corporate envelope expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
