<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pardis on Workspace</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/pardis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pardis on Workspace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 15:50:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/pardis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s the only way to be sure</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/04/19/its-the-only-way-to-be-sure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 15:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/04/19/its-the-only-way-to-be-sure/</guid>
      <description>At nearly thirty-seven thousand kilometres above southern Afghanistan, the geo-stationary WorkSpace relay milsat is a barely detectable stellar mote in the clear, frigid, night sky. Suspended in a cylindrical vat of liquid helium, and protected with a ring of bulky tanks of propellant, the mind of the satellite pulses gently with a superconductive glow. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t really think, WorkSpace tends to impose a strict AI capacity cap on geosynchronous weapons platforms with kinetic missile capability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratchet</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/03/08/ratchet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 13:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/03/08/ratchet/</guid>
      <description>Even with the pharmacological mitigation and enclosure comfort provided by the Job, therapy with my patients rarely shared the structured, ethereal angst of a first world counselling session. Dealing not with the maybe, the bogeymen of possibility, the faint spectre of disaster – all distant cousins to true pain; these fragmented souls had already seen and felt far too much real trauma to compare even fleetingly with my pampered albionside client base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Deconstructed Man</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/02/25/the-deconstructed-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 21:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/02/25/the-deconstructed-man/</guid>
      <description>The activated charcoal in the aircon had long since been active and the prefab smelled like camping trips and the drying wetsuit tang of childhood seaside visits. I pegged back the membrane door as far as it could go and we all shuffled in, Zalmai brought up the rear, taxiing reluctantly into the musty space. Currently our complement is only seven, a recent c.difficile outbreak resulted in two deaths – only one surprise, a goat farmer who wandered into the hospital compound unaided only missing a lung and his left hand – he died fours days later after the difficile infection swept opportunistically through the wards - a spectacular gastrointestinal revolt that left the whole ward retching and grieving in equal measure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empennage</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/02/24/empennage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 19:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/02/24/empennage/</guid>
      <description>Air quality permitting I try and hold the group sessions outside. When the particulate meter settles into a quasi-quiescent tick-tock metronome we bundle up the patients into hand-me-down NBCs and stretcher/carry/cajole our charges into the ambulance (an ungainly USMC anti-mine deuce and a half) and head south east to the poppy fields near the Khyber Pass. Since the mujahideen went synthetic savvy and the UNODC quashed production with the simple expedience of tactical nukes, the endless opium plantations have gone to seed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out patient</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/02/10/out-patient/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 22:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/02/10/out-patient/</guid>
      <description>13th January 2031
There is a certain weary comfort to a Monday morning here; despite the horrors in the prefabs and the faintly gamma-positive sleet pocking the poly roof of my office, I take some solace from the generic, familiar schlep of the starting week.
I had been up for three hours already, a nagging occipitalis ache dragging me neck first from an uneasy sleep on my surplus noncom cot. In contrast to my usual fractious, broken dreams, my office looked the same as always – a small pokey appendix epoxied to the back of the main ward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
