<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life After WorkSpace on Workspace</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/life-after-workspace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life After WorkSpace on Workspace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2009 15:58:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/life-after-workspace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deafblind date</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/08/02/deafblind-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2009 15:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/08/02/deafblind-date/</guid>
      <description>Brant has travelled a bit, some contracting work in China, a stint in South America with a backpack and whining Danish girlfriend, even some Provencal pretensions as an abortive property developer (Brant couldn’t spot a bear market if it chewed his face off) – he flattered himself that he had evolved a keen eye for difference. Over the years he has developed what he privately calls an interpretation filter (his internal geek is inherently polysyllabic), the quality and successes of which he sees varying wildly from country to country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brighton Run</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2009/07/11/brighton-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2009 11:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2009/07/11/brighton-run/</guid>
      <description>The liberti is called Daisy Longley. This fact (and several others) was delivered in a snivelly and hitched voice in between bouts of wretched crying in a Starbucks on Croydon High Street. Cradling a tall latte (extra hot, triple shot - her urban survival reflexes evidently still partially intact), and staring miserably into the middle distance, Daisy laboriously (and frankly after some time, boringly) relayed the events of the past hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piebald Piper</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/05/26/piebald-piper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 14:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/05/26/piebald-piper/</guid>
      <description>It’s been six months since He came to live in my head.
I was born deaf, an unfortunate genetic confluence called Waardenburg syndrome determined that I would never hear and never speak like you. I can talk after a fashion but the guttural qualities of my voice test the cursory patience of all but a few of the people I meet. I look a little odd too, not fairground grotesque but weird enough for most people to duck their heads or cross the road when I go out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acclimation</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/05/25/acclimation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 16:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/05/25/acclimation/</guid>
      <description>Agate thought she had adequately prepared for not working. For the past thirteen months she had been subsistence level living; no booze, no new media, base spec nourishment, she had even become an amateur seamstress: she had saved over a hundred thousand euros. Pre-resignation this had seemed like a huge amount, a chunky hedge against poverty and the hydra grasp of a taxation system seemingly designed to obviate all disposable income and still allow stinking piles of garbage to build up monthly on Leyton road where Agate rented her small apartment in the old Olympic village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This way to the egress</title>
      <link>https://example.com/2008/05/11/this-way-to-the-egress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/2008/05/11/this-way-to-the-egress/</guid>
      <description>The softly glowing virch pointer hovers for a long moment over the Send icon, then, with an involuntary anal clench she fiercely toggles the command.
Recipient: hr@workspace.co.uk Subject: Notice of resignation Importance: High
&amp;hellip;Message sent
She tears off the goggles with trembling hands, she hasn’t bothered to fully dunk to send the message; this morning, given her terminal intentions, she hadn’t considered it worthwhile prepping for full immersion.
The response, whilst not instantaneous (machine intelligence has to find time to interface with its tardy human counterparts), is violently swift.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
