<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>closed broadcast on WorkSpace</title>
    <link>/tags/closed-broadcast.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in closed broadcast on WorkSpace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2047 12:47:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/closed-broadcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&lt;Gabrielpost. closed broadcast|personal FB log.DATESTAMP: 12:47.12.12.47&gt;</title>
      <link>/warped/2047-12-12-closed-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.47.12.12.47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2047 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warped/2047-12-12-closed-broadcast-backchannel.datestamp-12.47.12.12.47.html</guid>
      <description>Jonty was braver than most. He shucked his Primarni eight quid tunic and then only hesitated briefly before climbing into the cutter on his hands and knees. He snagged his Skin on a lower part of the chassis, a crappy weld I remember promising myself I&amp;rsquo;d dremel off and never did, scoring a painless weld on his shoulder. Under the harsh sodiums the Skin disappointed me as it always does. Despite the profound amount of technology crammed (nano-wise and micro-ways) into its 6mm dermis, it screamed Gov issue drab; they never did pin down the self-cleaning routines and dirt that wont wash away was tattooed into the gross creases under his shoulder blades and elbows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;anotatepost. closed broadcast|personal FB log.NO DATESTAMP&gt;</title>
      <link>/warped/1970-01-01-closed-broadcast-personal-fb-log.no-datestamp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warped/1970-01-01-closed-broadcast-personal-fb-log.no-datestamp.html</guid>
      <description>Social historians looking back at the middle of 21C will perhaps puzzle at the predominance of starkly non-expressive faces in images or video captured in public places. As surveillance saturation increased from the early 2010s onwards, fuelled by ever granular taxing methods and notional terrorism threats, the general populace evolved means of reducing their biometric footprint. Gait modification trusses were at first home-brewed and then Chinese mass produced. After hoodies were outlawed grass roots lecture sessions on how to fool facial recognition software grew in popularity, and sign language jumped the gap from prosthesis to de facto language.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
